Southern New England Telephone Company Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Product Service Development, undated, 1889-1967
  - Blueprints and Diagrams (OS), Note: folders 2753-2761
    - Cable Diagrams - Orange/Derby (2), 1921 (Box (cab):, Folder 2756)
    - Cable Diagrams - Waterbury (2), 1921 (Box (cab):, Folder 2757)
    - Coy Switchboard Blueprint, 1878 (Box (cab):, Folder 2758)
    - Diagrams (Box (cab):, Folder 2759)
      - Connections in Trunk Line Section, 1889
      - Establishment of Exchange Trunk Connection (A,B), undated
      - Method of Wrapping Frayed Switchboard Cords, 1918
      - Schematic, 1906
      - Sketch Showing Method of Distribution from 10pr. Terminals, 1903
      - Sketch Showing Method of Supporting Cables and Proper Location, 1903
      - Sketch Showing Proposed Combination of Distribution, 1903
      - Standard Ground Connections, 1909
      - Standard Lag Screw for Six Pin Arm, 1902
      - Telephone Use Sign, undated
      - Test Section - Bridgeport, CT, undated
    - Loading Coil Vault/Manholes, 1921 (Box (cab):, Folder 2760)
    - Pay Stations, undated (Box (cab):, Folder 2761)
  - Cable Ledger New Haven Area w/maps, 1900-1906 (Box 292:, Folder 2762)
  - Cable Ledger New Haven Area, 1896-1913 (Box 292:, Folder 2763)
  - Carrier and Microwave Systems, 1967 (Box 292:, Folder 2764)
  - Cost Data for estimating the cost of new construction, 1925 (Box 292:, Folder 2765)
  - Equipment appraisal cards, ca. 1910-1915 (Box 292:, Folder 2766)
  - Engineering Department
    - File D4.1 Vol. No. 1, 1914-1930 (Box 292:, Folder 2767)
    - File D4.1 Vol. No. 2, 1913-1935 (Box 292:, Folder 2768)
    - File D4.2 Vol. No. 1 Retirement Costs, 1913-1931 (Box 293:, Folder 2769)
    - File D5.2 Vol. No. 1 Depreciation, 1913-1928 (Box 293:, Folder 2770)
    - File D5.2 Vol. No. 2 Depreciation Study, 1929 (Box 293:, Folder 2771)
    - File D5.2A A. F. Brooks Depreciation Testimony, 1928 (Box 293:, Folder 2772)
    - File D5.2A General and Correspondence, 1928 (Box 293:, Folder 2773)
    - File D6.1 Vol. No. 1 Depreciation Reserve Requirements Study, 1933 (Box 293:, Folder 2774)
    - File D6.1 Vol. No. 2 Depreciation Reserve Data, 1933-1936 (Box 293:, Folder 2775)
    - File D6.1 Vol. No. 3 Depreciation Reserve Requirement Study, 1936-1938 (Box 293:, Folder 2776)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 6 Retirement Unit Costs/Plant Quantities, 1921-1924 (Box 293:, Folder 2777)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 7 Retirement Unit Costs/Plant Quantities, 1925-1927 (Box 293:, Folder 2778)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 8 Preliminary Unit Costs, 1927-1933 (Box 294:, Folder 2779)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 9 Retirement Unit Costs, 1923-1932 (Box 294:, Folder 2780)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 13 Retirement Unit Costs, 1935-1937 (Box 294:, Folder 2781)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 14 Retirement Unit Cost Data, 1937 (Box 294:, Folder 2782)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 15 Retirement Accounting Practices, 1938 (Box 294:, Folder 2783)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 16 Station Apparatus, 1929-1941 (Box 294:, Folder 2784)
    - File PE11 Vol. No. 17 Preliminary Unit Costs, 1939-1941 (Box 294:, Folder 2785)
  - General Specifications for Exchange Aerial Construction, 1911 (Box 294:, Folder 2786)
  - Ledger Material/Labor, 1913-1915 (Box 294:, Folder 2787)
  - Major Emergency Routine, 1954 (Box 294:, Folder 2788)
  - Plant Bulletin - No. 1, 1910 (Box 294:, Folder 2789)
  - Plant Bulletin - Plainville, 1911-1922 (Box 294:, Folder 2790-91)
    - Inventories
      - Bristol Substation Inventory data sheets, 1917 (Box 295:, Folder 2792)
      - Notes on Inventories, Separation of Toll and Exchange Plant, Etc., 1913 (Box 295:, Folder 2793)
      - Pole Line, Aerial Wire and Aerial Cable Plant Inventory (Box 295:, Folder 2794)
        - Hamden and Canal RR, 1917
        - New Haven, 1917 (Box 295:, Folder 2795)
        - Waterbury, 1921 (Box 295:, Folder 2796)
        - Willimantic, 1916 (Box 296:, Folder 2797-98)
          - Plant Department Inventory, 1916 (Box 296:, Folder 2799-805)
- Series V: Studies, Reports, and Plans, undated, 1911-1985
  - Paper
    - Administrative Routine for Approval of Time Share Projects, 1976 (Box 297:, Folder 2806)
    - Automatic Number Identification, 1960? (Box 297:, Folder 2807)
    - CAMA Studies (Centralized Automatic Message Accounting), 1956-1961 (Box 297:, Folder 2810)
    - CAROT II - Centralized Automatic Reporting on Trunks - Phase 2, 1975 (Box 297:, Folder 2811)
    - Conduit Study - data, 1942 (Box 297:, Folder 2812)
      see also: box 303
    - Connecticut - Census of Manufacturers, 1939 (Box 297:, Folder 2813)
    - Connecticut Control Switch Point Study, 1964 (Box 297:, Folder 2814)
    - Connecticut Regional Survey, 1929-1950 (Box 297:, Folder 2815)
    - Data and Information Systems (Information Technology Learning Center)
      - 1974 Objectives - Status Report (Box 297:, Folder 2818)
      - 1974 Project Summary (Box 297:, Folder 2819)
      - 1975 Objectives - Mid Year Report (Box 297:, Folder 2820)
      - 1975 Objectives - Year End Report (Box 297:, Folder 2821)
      - 1975 Project Summary (Box 297:, Folder 2822)
      - 1976 Objectives - Mid year Report (Box 297:, Folder 2823)
      - 1976 Objectives - Year End Report (Box 297:, Folder 2824)
      - 1976 Project Summary (Box 297:, Folder 2825)
      - 1977 Objectives - Mid Year Report (Box 297:, Folder 2826)
      - 1977 Objectives - Year End Report (Box 297:, Folder 2827)
      - 1978 Objectives - Mid Year Report (Box 297:, Folder 2828)
      - 1978 Objectives - Year End Report (Box 297:, Folder 2829)
      - 1979 Objectives - Mid Year Report (Box 297:, Folder 2830)
      - 1979 Objectives - Year End Report (Box 297:, Folder 2831)
      - 1980 Objectives - Mid Year Report (Box 297:, Folder 2832)
    - Data and Information Systems (Information Technology Center)
      - 1980 Objectives - Year End Report, 1981 (Box 297:, Folder 2833)
      - 1981 Objectives - Mid Year Report (Box 297:, Folder 2834)
      - 1981 Objectives - Year End Report, 1982 (Box 297:, Folder 2835)
      - 1982 Objectives - Mid Year Report (Box 297:, Folder 2836)
      - 1981 Departmental MBO Review, 1981 January - June (Box 297:, Folder 2839)
      - 1982 Departmental MBO Review, 1982 January - June (Box 297:, Folder 2840)
      - 1982 Departmental MBO Review, 1982 janaury - December (Box 297:, Folder 2841)
      - Corporate Mechanization Program Annual Report - Projects Cut into Service, 1978 (Box 297:, Folder 2849)
      - Corporate Mechanization Program Annual Report - Projects Cut into Service, 1979 (Box 297:, Folder 2850)
      - CRIS Division, Work Program Status Report for the First Half of 1982 (Box 297:, Folder 2851)
    - Direct Distance Dialing - Northwest Study, 1959 (Box 297:, Folder 2853)
    - Directory Assistance Charging
      - Business Customer Survey, 1973 (Box 297:, Folder 2854)
      - Charging for Directory Assistance, 1974 (Box 297:, Folder 2855)
      - Charging for Directory Assistance - Rate Recommendation, 1976 (Box 297:, Folder 2856)
      - Charging for Directory Assistance - Replies to the PUCA Questions, 1976 March (Box 297:, Folder 2857)
      - Charging for Directory Assistance - Replies to the PUCA Questions, 1976 June (Box 297:, Folder 2858)
      - Directory Assistance Charging, undated (Box 297:, Folder 2859)
      - Directory Assistance Charging Curtailment Study - 6 Proposed Rate Plans, 1976 (Box 297:, Folder 2860)
      - Directory Assistance Charging - a Research Proposal, 1972 (Box 298:, Folder 2861)
      - Directory Assistance Charging - An SNET Public Relations Plan to Inform Employees - Public, 1978 (Box 298:, Folder 2862)
      - Directory Assistance Charging Study - Rate Case Data, 1975 (Box 298:, Folder 2863)
      - Directory Assistance Charging - 1976 Study (Box 298:, Folder 2864-65)
      - Directory Assistance Charging - 1978 Study (Box 298:, Folder 2866)
      - Directory Assistance System/Microfilm - Operational and Economic Analysis, 1974 (Box 298:, Folder 2867)
      - Directory Assistance Usage Study, 1976 (Box 298:, Folder 2868)
      - Directory Assistance Usage Characteristics Study, 1976 (Box 298:, Folder 2869)
      - Effectiveness of Directory Assistance Volume Reduction Advertising, May to October 1977, 1978 (Box 298:, Folder 2870)
      - General, undated, 1976-1978 (Box 298:, Folder 2871)
      - Heuristic Estimation of SNET Directory Assistance Charging Curtailment - 5 Alternate Rate Plans, 1975 (Box 298:, Folder 2872)
      - Introducing the X-Y-Z Directory Assistance Pos., undated (Box 298:, Folder 2873)
      - Residence Customer Survey, 1973 (Box 298:, Folder 2874)
      - Service and Cost Analysis, 1977 (Box 298:, Folder 2875)
    - Division Operations Managers, 1969-1971 (Box 298:, Folder 2876)
    - Division of Revenues Study - Central Office Equipment, 1943 (Box 298:, Folder 2877)
    - Downstate High Density Backbone Routing Strategies, 1981 (Box 298:, Folder 2878)
      (New York Telephone)
    - Earnings and Profit Study - Farmington Valley Telephone Co., 1967? (Box 298:, Folder 2879-80)
    - Earnings and Profit Study - Farmington Valley Telephone Co., 1967? (Box 299:, Folder 2881-82)
    - Earnings and Profit Study - Sharon Telephone Co., 1969? (Box 299:, Folder 2883-85)
      - Sharon Telephone Co. - Financial Statements, 1909-1923 (Box 299:, Folder 2886)
    - Earnings and Profit Study - Sharon Telephone Co., 1974? (Box 299:, Folder 2887-88)
    - Fiber Backbone Routing Strategies, 1982 (Box 299:, Folder 2900)
    - Foreign Corrupt Practices Act- Plan for Compliance, [1978?] (Box 299:, Folder 2901)
    - Fundamental Plan for the Administration of Customer Services, 1974 (Box 299:, Folder 2902)
    - Gasoline Rationing, 1980 (Box 299:, Folder 2903)
    - Hartford Metropolitan Area Plan, 1976 (Box 299:, Folder 2904)
    - Index Number Study, Aerial Cable, 1925 (Box 300:, Folder 2905)
      - Poles, 1925 (Box 300:, Folder 2906)
      - Poles Removed, 1925 (Box 300:, Folder 2907)
    - Interoffice Lightguide Backbone Facility Route, 1982 (Box 300:, Folder 2909)
      - Hartford Area Inter-Office Plan, 1981 (Box 300:, Folder 2910)
      - Local Area Networks, 1982 (Box 300:, Folder 2911)
    - Long Range Planning for Plant Extension, 1973 (Box 300:, Folder 2912-14)
    - Microwave Fundamental Plan, 1966 (Box 300:, Folder 2915)
    - New London District - Plans and Objectives for 1970 (Box 300:, Folder 2916)
    - Old Greenwich Sound Beach Study, 1911-1917 (Box 300:, Folder 2917)
    - Opportunities for Increasing Organizational Effectiveness (Arthur D. Little, Inc.), 1963 (Box 300:, Folder 2918)
    - Performance Review, 1979 (Box 300:, Folder 2919)
    - Planning for a Digital Backbone Facility, 1982? (Box 300:, Folder 2920)
    - Planning Material for Phase 1 of the Customer Request for Service Segment of the Business Information System, 1965 (Box 300:, Folder 2921)
    - Public Utilities Commission Docket no.7415 - Separation of Property, Expenses and Revenues, (vol. 1), 1946 (Box 300:, Folder 2931)
    - Public Utilities Commission Docket no.7415 - Separation of Property, Expenses and Revenues, (vol. 2), 1946 (Box 300:, Folder 2932-33)
    - Public Utilities Commission Docket no.7415 - Separation of Property, Expenses and Revenues - Central Office Equipment, 1946 (Box 301:, Folder 2934)
    - The Road After 1984: The Impact of Technology on Society - A Nation-Wide Survey of the Public and Its Leaders on the New Technology and Its Consequences for American Life (Louis Harris and Assoc. Inc.), 1983 (Box 301:, Folder 2935)
      - Survey Data
      - Impact of Technology on Society (Connecticut), 1983 (Box 301:, Folder 2936-37)
      - Impact of Technology on Society (Leaders), 1983 (Box 301:, Folder 2938-39)
      - Impact of Technology on Society (Public), 1983 (Box 301:, Folder 2940-41)
    - SNET Testing Utilities, undated (Box 301:, Folder 2943)
    - Southern New England Telephone Cellular Mobile Telecommunications Service - A Case Study (Presented at Yale School of Organization and Management), 1985 (Box 301:, Folder 2944)
    - Special Service - Serving Plan, 1981 (Box 302:, Folder 2945)
    - Studies filed with the PUCA/DPUC, 1975-1979 (Box 302:, Folder 2946-53)
    - Studies and Reports filed with the PUCA/DPUC, 1975-1979 (Box 302:, Folder 2954-61)
    - Studies and Reports filed with the PUCA/DPUC, 1975-1979 (Box 545:, Folder 2962-63)
    - Summaries of Typical Business Research Studies, [1974?] (Box 545:, Folder 2964)
    - Summary of General Business Conditions in Connecticut, 1946 (Box 545:, Folder 2965)
    - SXS Intertoll Tandem Retirements, 1975-1976 (Box 545:, Folder 2966)
    - SXS Tandem Replacements, 1973-1976 (Box 545:, Folder 2967)
    - Tariff divestiture
      - Interoffice Facility Study, 1980 (Box 545:, Folder 2968)
      - T1C vs. T1, 1979 (Box 545:, Folder 2969)
    - Terrestrial Digital Circuits Filing
      - Vol. 2 Demand Analysis Process and Results, 1982 (Box 545:, Folder 2970)
      - Vol. 4 High Capacity Investment Generator System, 1982 (Box 545:, Folder 2971)
    - Unit Cost Studies, 1917-1918 (Box 545:, Folder 2972)
    - Unit Cost Studies, 1917-1918 (Box 546:, Folder 2973)
      - Conduit Study - Data (OS), 1942; note: see box 303, folder 2974
      - Installation Man Hours, 1919-1920 (Box 546:, Folder 2975)
      - Original Derivation of Construction Unit Cost, 1915-1924 (Box 546:, Folder 2976)
      - Terminal Study (OS), [1917-1918?]; note: see box 303, folder 2977
  - Oversize
    - Conduit Study - Data, 1942 (Box 303:, Folder 2974)
    - Terminal Study, [1917-18?] (Box 303:, Folder 2977)
- Project Management Reports - Fiche
  PR = performance reviews
  DEF = Definition reports
  DES = Design reports
  FO = Formation reports
  ST = Status Reports
  - P # 8017 (Box 304)
    - 101 ESS (electronic switching system) ST, 1965
    - ACCOUNT 725 PR, DSG, 1975-77
    - AID (assignment information display) ST, 1979
    - AID (assignment information display) FO, 1979
    - AIS (automatic interface system) ST, 1977
    - ALSTON RECORDERS FO, DEF/DSG, PR, ST, 1975-1977
    - AMA (automatic message accounting) DEF, 1973
    - AMA One Second Timing (automatic message accounting) PR, 1974
    - AT&T EDP Systems Council 1 ST, 1975
    - Basic R&C (reconciliation and conversion) ST, 1975
    - Billing and Collecting ST, 1974
    - BISCOM (business information system communications system) DSG, 1970
    - BISCUS (business information systems customers service) pre/DEF, DSG, pre/DSG, 1968-1969
    - BISCUS/FACS (business information system customer facility assignment and control system) ST, 1976-1977
    - BISCUS/FACS (business information system customer facility assignment and control system) ST, 1977
    - BISP Plan ST, 1978
    - BOBS (business office business sales) PR, DEF/DSG, 1977, 1979
    - BOCAP (business office cost analysis plan) DEF/DSG, 1978
    - BRED 1 (bill redesign phase 1) FO, 1977
    - BRED II (bill redesign) FO, 1978
    - BSCRR (business service center records reorganization) FO, 1979
    - BSCRR (business service center records reorganization) DEF/DSG, 1979
    - BSC/RSC (business service center/residence service center conversion) ST, [1980?]
    - BSMP (billing service measurement plan) ST,FO, 1979
    - CAAS (construction program administration system) DEF, 1971
    - CAM (connection appraisal methods program) FO, 1969
    - CAMA-C (centralized automatic message accounting - Computerized) PR, 1977
    - CAMIS (construction activities management information System) FO, 1979
    - CAPS (centrex and PBX systems) ST, DES, 1973-1976
    - CAPS PR, 1978
    - CAPS Multistation FO,ST,PR/ST, PR, 1977-1979
    - CARE (computer administration report and evaluation) FO,ST, 1974
    - Cash Redesign ST, 1980
    - CCAUP (computerized cable upkeep administrative program) FO, 1976
    - CCSA and FX Detail FO/DES, PR, 1974-1975
    - CDM (cost distribution module) FO, 1980
    - Centralized Mail Remittance Mechanization PR,FO, 1971-1973
    - Centrex Conv. System ST, PR, FO, 1973-1976
    - Centrex Feature Addition DEF/DSG, 1978
    - CISRP (customer installation service results plan) FO, PR, 1975-1976
    - CMDS 1 (Centralized message data system) ST, 1968
    - CMDS II (Centralized message data system - phase 2) ST, 1968
    - CMDS/EMR (centralized message data system/ expanded Message record) FO, DEF/DSG, 1978-1980
    - CMR (centralized mail remittance mechanization), 1972
    - CNA (customer name and address microfilm application) ST,ST,FO, 1971-1977
    - CNA (customer name and address) DEF/DSG, 1977
    - COER (#5 central office equipment reports) PR, 1975
    - COER (#5 crossbar engineering and administration) FO/DSG, 1973
    - COIN (coin revenues) FO, 1972
    - COIN (coin phone operational and information network) ST, 1969-1972
    - COIN/CTOCS (coin telephone operational and information Network/coin telephone operation center subsystem) DEF/DSG, 1978-1979
    - COMBO DES, ST, 1977
    - COMLIST (company mailing lists) PR, 1974
    - Comptrollers Conference ST, 1977
    - Computer Planning ST, 1971
    - CONVESS (conversion to ESS) DES, PR, undated, 1972-1974
    - CONVESS II (conversion to ESS) FO, PR, 1975-1976
    - Corporate Securities ST, 1979
    - COSAU (company savings plan) ST, PR, 1978-1979
    - COSAV (company savings plan) DES, FO/DEF, 1976-1978
    - CPR-COE (continuing property records) ST, 1979
    - CRB Misc. Expense Controls ST, 1968
    - CRB Report Requirements (customer record and billing) ST, 1967
    - CRIS (customer record information system) ST, 1977
    - CRISSOUP (customer records information system service Order update) ST, FO/DEF, DSG, 1977-1979
    - Cross Bar Random Administration System DES, ST, PR, 1973-1975
    - CTR (current time report) FO,DSG/ST Network/coin telephone operation center subsystem) ST,FO, 1975-1976
    - Customer Records Information System FO, 1977
    - CWM (redesign of clerical work measurement reporting System) DSG, PR, 1977-1978
    - DAS/M (directory assistance system/ microfiche) ST, 1973
    - DATA PAC DEF/DSG, PR, ST, 1972-1975
    - Database Management Billing and Collecting FO, 1972
    - DDS SVCS Bureau FO, PR, 1970-1972
    - Deferral Accounting FO, 1976
    - DILSO ST, 1963
    - Directory Assistance Charging FO, 1972
    - Directory Assistance Charging Studies DSG, 1975
    - Directory Assistance on Monthly Analysis #9 Rpt FO, 1975
    - Directory Assistance Statistics PR, 1975
    - Directory Delivery DEF, 1976
    - Directory Delivery System FO,DSG, PR, 1975-1978
    - DOPAC (disk oriented property and cost system) FO, 1969
    - DR2020 PR, 1972
    - DSDOPAC DSG, 1977
    - DSP (division sales plan) FO, DSG, ST, PR, 1974-1977
    - DSP Modification (division sales plan) DEF/DSG, 1976
    - DSP Phone Center Modification (division sales plan) FO, 1977
    - EAS (engineering administration system) FO, 1973
    - ECOS (emission control operational survey system) DSG, 1973
    - EDP Long Range Plan) ST, 1973
    - EIS (expenditure information system) ST, 1972
    - EIS II (expenditure information system II) FO, 1972
    - ERS (employee record study) DEF, ST, [1979?]-1980
    - ESS ST, PR, 1971-1977
    - EWM PR, 1978
    - FA/NAP (functional accounting & network access pricing) ST, 1972
    - FA/Payroll DEF, DSG/ST, 1975-1977
    - FA STAGE II (functional accounting) ST, 1975
    - FAINT-REL 7 (functional accounting interface design report-Product release 7) DSG, 1978
    - FAINT-REL 107 (functional accounting interface design report-Product release 10) DSG, 1979
    - Functional Accounting ST, FO, 1976-1978
    - GIS-CRSE ST, 1973
    - GRI 75 (retention and refund) ST, 1975
    - GRI 75 (overview of data systems rate case involvement) ST, 1975
    - HAIR Refund ST, 1969
    - ICH (international call handling) FO,ST, 1975-1976
    - Intrastate Inwats ST, 1966
    - ICIS (investment and cost information system) ST, 1968-1969
    - ICIS (investment and cost information system- system Description guide) ST, 1974
    - Interexchange & Intraexchange Facilities FO, DSG, ST, 1974
    - LATIS (loop activity tracking information system) FO, ST, 1980
    - LMOS (loop maintenance operation system) FO, DEF, 1975-1976
    - Mail Enclosing ST, 1969
    - MAP/NAT (mechanized accounts payable/national vendor Tracking) FO, ST, FO/DEF, 1978-1979
    - MARS/SXS (mechanized assignment and records system for step by step) FO, 1980
    - MBO (management by objective) ST, 1973
    - Measured Service ST, 1971
    - Mechanized Corp Accounting FO, 1978
    - Mechanized Furniture CPR FO, 1973
    - Mechanized Line Cards FO, 1972
    - Mechanized Station Inventory ST, 1971-1973
    - Mechanized Treatment DSG, PR, undated, 1974
    - Mini Computer Information ST, 1972
    - MIS (marketing information system) FO, ST, 1973
    - MIS/RJE FO, 1973
    - Misc. Expense Controls ST, 1968
    - MLT (mechanized loop testing) FO, DSG, [1976?]-1978
    - MMS (marketing measurement system) FO/DEF, DSG, ST, PR, 1976-1978
    - MPEX DSG, 1971
    - MOMBO (mechanization of manual billing operations) ST, 1979
    - MOST (mechanization of stockholder transactions) DEF/DSG, ST, 1968-1969
    - MOVIMS (motor vehicle information system) FO, ST, 1973-1978
    - MOVIMS Interface FO, 1978
    - MSS (mechanized special studies system) DEF/DSG, FO, 1979
    - MTRIS (major tool reconciliation of inventory system) DEF, DSG,PR, 1972-1974
    - MTSS (marketing toll study system) FO, undated
    - OACS (optional area calling service) DSG, 1974
    - OC-C (other charges and credit to customer records database) FO, 1979
    - PASSBAR (plant and switching system budget and results) DEF, DSG, PR, 1971-1977
    - PASSBAR II (plant and switching system budget and results) DSG, DEF,ST, 1977-1979
    - PCAVES PR, 1971
    - PDS (personnel data system) FO, DEF, ST, DSG, PR, 1971-1974
    - Pensions DEF/DSG, ST, FO, PR, DSG, 1972-1979
    - Pensions Rewrite DEF/DSG, undated
    - PICS/DCPR (plug in control system/ detailed continuing property Record) FO/ST, 1979
    - Pole Records Com DSG, 1973
    - Pole Records CATV PR, 1974
    - POLECAT (pole records CATV) FO, DEF, PR/ST, 1971-1974
    - POLECAT VER II ((pole records CATV) FO, undated
    - PROJECT I (mechanization of a standard order flow for special Services) ST, DEF/DSG, 1970-1974
    - PROJECT II (online circuit order production system) FO, DSG, 1974-1978
    - PSC/CIS (preferred stock changes and common issue system) ST, PR, 1974-1976
    - PSS (pension status system) FO, DSG, 1975
    - PTSC (public telephone service center) DEF/DSG, FO, DSG, 1979-1980
    - PTSC PH III (public telephone service center) DSG, 1980
    - Purchase Order Tracking ST, FO, 1978-1979
    - Records Reconciliation FO/DEF, DSG, ST, PR, 1976-1979
    - Redemp. Of Pref. Shares (redemption of preferred shares) FO, DEF/DSG, 1979
    - ROACS (rerating optional area calling service) DEF/DSG, PR, ST, 1974-1975
    - RECON 122 (reconciliation of account 122-21 expenditures) FO, DSG, ST, PR, 1973-1978
    - Restructure Interstate WATS DSG, PR, 1974-1975
    - Redesign of Clerical Work Measurement Reporting System FO, 1976
    - R & C Reduction Rec. (R & C reduction recommendations) ST, [1975]
    - SEAR (SNET employee activity report) FO, DEF, DSG, PR, 1976-1979
    - Service Center Planning Project Team ST, 1973
    - SECRET (SONAR error correction re-entry) FO/DEF, DSG, 1978-1979
    - SECRET PHASE I (SONAR error correction re-entry) DSG, 1979
    - SHARPPS (shareholder automatic reinvestment and purchase plan System) DEF, ST, PR, 1975-1977
    - SIM (system for intercept mechanization) FO/DEF, DSG, PR, 1973-1976
    - SN 995 (SN 995 financial report) FO, 1980
    - SODA (service order dial administration) FO, DEF/DSG, 1977-1978
    - SOF (service order filing) FO, DSG, 1975-1977
    - SONAR (service order network administration and reports) FO, DEF, DSG, 1973-1975